{
    "subject": "resource/Ratatat",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Ratatat is from United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8292266726493835,
            "question": "Where is Ratatat from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6194043755531311,
            "question": "What country are Ratatat associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5945934653282166,
            "question": "When was Ratatat formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4843425750732422,
            "question": "Are there any famous members of Ratatat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.461465984582901,
            "question": "Where have Ratatat performed live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40990012884140015,
            "question": "Is Ratatat a band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3529717028141022,
            "question": "Has Ratatat won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27748343348503113,
            "question": "What are some popular songs by Ratatat?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2603527009487152,
            "question": "What instruments do the members of Ratatat play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.24354954063892365,
            "question": "What kind of music does Ratatat play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ratatat is from United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8920_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What instruments do the members of Ratatat play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8920_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular songs by Ratatat?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8920_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Ratatat won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8920_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8920_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently state that Ratatat is an American band based in Brooklyn, New York. This information supports the statement that Ratatat is from the United States."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}